[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone. <br /><br />Click \"Continue\" when you're ready to move on.","rt":37097,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":62267,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</ sub>, yo u start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":8068,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":70338,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":1827,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":72169,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":3279,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":75451,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1320,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":76778,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":5626,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":82409,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":1196,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":83608,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":3705,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":87316,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1097,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":88417,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bi gger, yo u subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":1674,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":90097,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":1349,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":91449,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":1895,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":93347,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":1057,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":94408,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":1942,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":96353,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":1089,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":97455,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<su b>6</sub >, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":1942,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":99400,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1084,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":100488,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":1734,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":102226,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1184,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":103414,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":2606,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":106024,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":918,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":106949,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":12908,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":119861,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the thing that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its  own inv erse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":17936,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":137801,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":3342,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":141146,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1172,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":142321,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is th e thing  which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":1590,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":143915,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":985,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":144905,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":1206,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":146114,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The  inverse  of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1023,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":147141,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":1673,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":148822,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":789,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":149616,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember,  the inv erse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":1792,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":151416,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":3042,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":154462,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"Let's review: under +<sub>6</sub>, the inverse of 0 is 0, the inverse of 1 is 5 and the inverse of 5 is 1, the inverse of 2 is 4 and the inverse of 4 is 2, and finally the inverse of 3 is 3. Do you see a relationship between an element and its inverse under +<sub>6</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"The 2 numbers sum t o 6, exc ept for 0.","response_history":["The 2 numbers sum to 6, except for 0."],"rt":28927,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":183395,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":15232,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":198631,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</ sub> 1 + <sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because of this, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":44387,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":243021,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":8498,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":251525,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 u sing jus t 3.","rt":1633,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":253161,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":1856,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":255021,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":15303,"trial_type":"feedba ck","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":270328,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":4090,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":274423,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":1390,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":275817,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","N o"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":3432,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":279253,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":992,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":280254,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Let's review: under +<sub>6</sub>, 1 and 5 are generators. However, 0, 2, 3, and 4 are not generators. Try playing with these non-generators and seeing which elements each of them does generate (i.e. which elements you can get by combining each non-generator with itself repeatedly). Do you see relationships among particular subsets of the elements that are not generators under +<sub>6</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Even numbers are not generators with  +6.","response_history":["zE","z","Even numbers are not generators when the ","Even numbers are not generators wh","Even numbers are not generators with +6."],"rt":30036,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":310293,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":11135,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":321431,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 ","response_history":["1"],"rt":3288,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":324724,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":858,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":325587,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":2480,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":328070,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":2365,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":330439,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":2012,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":332455,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":1618,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":334076,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":2158,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":336238,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"5.  4 + 1 is 5, which is less than 9, so I don't subtract 9.","response_history":["5.   $ ","5.  $","5.  4 + 1 is 5, which is less than9","5.  4 + 1 is 5, which is less than 9, so I don't subr","5.  4 + 1 is 5, which is less than 9, so I don't subtract 9."],"rt":16699,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":352940,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"3.  4 + 8 is 12, which is greater than 9, so I subtract 9.","response_history":["3.  4 + 8 is 12, which is greater than 9, so I subtract 9."],"rt":13728,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":366672,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0.  When you combine it with another number, you get the same nu mber bac k.","response_history":["0.  When you combine it with another number, you get teh sa","0.  When you combine it with another number, you get teh s","0.  When you combine it with another number, you get teh ","0.  When you combine it with another number, you get teh","0.  When you combine it with another number, you get te","0.  When you combine it with another number, you get the same number bacvk.","0.  When you combine it with another number, you get the same number bacvk","0.  When you combine it with another number, you get the same number bacv","0.  When you combine it with another number, you get the same number back."],"rt":40660,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":407343,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":13650,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":420997,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","response_history":["7"],"rt":2832,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":423834,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"6.  3 + 6 = 9, which results in 0 (the identity) when you subtract 9.","response_history":["6.  # ","6.  #","6.  3 + 6 = 9, which results in 0 (the identity).","6.  3 + 6 = 9, which results in 0 (the identity) .","6.  3 + 6 = 9, which results in 0 (the identity) w.","6.  3 + 6 = 9, which results in 0 (the identity) wh.","6.  3 + 6 = 9, which results in 0 (the identity) whe.","6.  3 + 6 = 9, which results in 0 (the identity) when .","6.  3  + 6 = 9,  which results in 0 (the identity) when y.","6.  3 + 6 = 9, which results in 0 (the identity) when you.","6.  3 + 6 = 9, which results in 0 (the identity) when you .","6.  3 + 6 = 9, which results in 0 (the identity) when you su.","6.  3 + 6 = 9, which results in 0 (the identity) when you sub.","6.  3 + 6 = 9, which results in 0 (the identity) when you subt.","6.  3 + 6 = 9, which results in 0 (the identity) when you subtr.","6.  3 + 6 = 9, which results in 0 (the identity) when you subtra.","6.  3 + 6 = 9, which results in 0 (the identity) when you subtrac.","6.  3 + 6 = 9, which results in 0 (the identity) when you subtract.","6.  3 + 6 = 9, which results in 0 (the identity) when you subtract .","6.  3 + 6 = 9, which results in 0 (the identity) when you subtract 9."],"rt":25705,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":449543,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how y ou got y our answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Yes.  Every other number can be made with 2 since 2 is even and 9 is odd.","response_history":["Yes.  Every other number can e ","Yes.  Every other number can e","Yes.  Every other number can be made with 2 since t","Yes.  Every other number can be made with 2 since 2 is even and 9 is odd."],"rt":18738,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":468285,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No.  You cannot produce all #'s with 2 odds.","response_history":["No.  2 ","No.  2","No.  you can","No.  you ca","No.  you c","No.  you ","No.  you","No.  yo","No.  y","No.  You can ","No.  You cannot produce all #'s with 2 odds."],"rt":24486,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":492777,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Yes.  You will get 5, 1, 6, 2, 7, 3, 8, 4, and 0 as you add 5's.","response_history":["No,. ","No,.","No,","No.  You cannot produce all #'s 0=-","No.  You cannot produce all #'s 0=","No.  You cannot produce all #'s 0-9 with 2 odds.  You will get 5, 1, 6, 2, 7, 3, 8, 4, and 0 as you add 5's.","Y.  You will get 5, 1, 6, 2, 7, 3, 8, 4, and 0 as you add 5's.","Ye.  You will get 5, 1, 6, 2, 7, 3, 8, 4, and 0 as you add 5's.","Yes.  You will get 5, 1, 6, 2, 7, 3, 8, 4, and 0 as you add 5's."],"rt":106309,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":599091,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No. You will get 6, 3, 0, 6, 3, 0, etc.","response_history":["You will get 6, 3, 0, 6, 3, 0, etc.","NYou will get 6, 3, 0, 6, 3, 0, etc.","NoYou will get 6, 3, 0, 6, 3, 0, etc.","No. You will get 6, 3, 0, 6, 3, 0, etc."],"rt":48669,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":647764,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use \"+_n\", and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":50745,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":698515,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"0 = 1 +_n(n-1)","response_history":["0 = 1 + ","0 = 1 ++","0 = 1 +_n(n-1)"],"rt":30604,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":729124,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"0 = x +_n(n - x).  The 2 numbers must sum to get n to return the identity (0).  So for a +_n base, the number added to x will be n - x.","response_history":["0 = +_n(n - x).  The 2 numbers must sum to get n to return the identity (9)","0 = +_n(n - x).  The 2 numbers must sum to get n to return the identity (9","0 = +_n(n - x).  The 2 numbers must sum to get n to return the identity (0).  Sof r a","0 = +_n(n - x).  The 2 numbers must sum to get n to return the identity (0).  Sof r ","0 = +_n(n - x).  The 2 numbers must sum to ge t n to r eturn the identity (0).  Sof r","0 = +_n(n - x).  The 2 numbers must sum to get n to return the identity (0).  Sof ","0 = +_n(n - x).  The 2 numbers must sum to get n to return the identity (0).  Sof","0 = +_n(n - x).  The 2 numbers must sum to get n to return the identity (0).  So for a +_n base, x ","0 = +_n(n - x).  The 2 numbers must sum to get n to return the identity (0).  So for a +_n base, x","0 = +_n(n - x).  The 2 numbers must sum to get n to return the identity (0).  So for a +_n base, ","0 = x+_n(n - x).  The 2 numbers must sum to get n to return the identity (0).  So for a +_n base, ","0 = x +_n(n - x).  The 2 numbers must sum to get n to return the identity (0).  So for a +_n base, the nubmer","0 = x +_n(n - x).  The 2 numbers must sum to get n to return the identity (0).  So for a +_n base, the nubme","0 = x +_n(n - x).  The 2 numbers must sum to get n to return the identity (0).  So for a +_n base, the nubm","0 = x +_n(n - x).  The 2 numbers must sum to get n  to retu rn the identity (0).  So for a +_n base, the nub","0 = x +_n(n - x).  The 2 numbers must sum to get n to return the identity (0).  So for a +_n base, the nu","0 = x +_n(n - x).  The 2 numbers must sum to get n to return the identity (0).  So for a +_n base, the number added to x will be n - x."],"rt":94479,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":823610,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I believe that n - x has to be an odd number.  If n - x is even, it will never be a generator.","response_history":["I believe that n - x has to be a ","I believe that n - x has to be an odd nub","I believe that n - x has to be an odd number.  If n - x is even, it will never be a genr","I belie ve that  n - x has to be an odd number.  If n - x is even, it will never be a generator."],"rt":52559,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":876173,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":5117,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":881294,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":18399,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":899698,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator un der +<su b>n</sub>, x must divide n.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":11087,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":910790,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words why your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"True","response":"Take the example of n = 7 and x = 5.  The series would be:5, 5 +_7 5 = 3, 5 + _7 5 + _7 5 = 4, 5 + _7 5 + _7 5 + _7 5 = 6, ","response_history":["Tk","T","a","Tkae ","Tkae","Tka","Tk","Take example ","Take ","Take the example of n = 7 and x = 5.  The series would be 5 + 5_","Take the example of n = 7 and x = 5.  The series would be 5 + 5","Take the example of n = 7 and x = 5.  The series would be 5 + _7","Take the example of n = 7 and x = 5.  T he serie s would be 5 + _","Take the example of n = 7 and x = 5.  The series would be 5 + ","Take the example of n = 7 and x = 5.  The series would be 5 +_7 5 = 3","Take the example of n = 7 and x = 5.  The series would be 5 +","Take the example of n = 7 and x = 5.  The series would be 5 ","Take the example of n = 7 and x = 5.  The series would be 5, 5 +_7 5 = 3, 5 + _7 5 + _7 5 = 1, 5 + _7 5 + _7 5 + _7 5 = 6, ","Take the example of n = 7 and x = 5.  The series would be 5, 5 +_7 5 = 3, 5 + _7 5 + _7 5 = 4, 5 + _7 5 + _7 5 + _7 5 = 6, ","Take the example of n = 7 and x = 5.  The series would be: 5, 5 +_7 5 = 3, 5 + _7 5 + _7 5 = 4, 5 + _7 5 + _7 5 + _7 5 = 6, ","Take the example of n = 7 and x = 5.  The series would be:5, 5 +_7 5 = 3, 5 + _7 5 + _7 5 = 4, 5 + _7 5 + _7 5 + _7 5 = 6, "],"rt":168996,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":1079789,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is it s invers e a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":23564,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":1103358,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words why your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"sometimes","response":"My last answer wasn't complete . . . I thought I could insert line breaks with the Enter key.  I believe it is always a generator.  This is the formula shown in the generator definition.","response_history":["Sometimes ","Sometimes.  ","My last answer wasn't complete . . .I","My last answer wasn't complete . . . I thought I could ins","My last answ er wasn' t complete . . . I thought I could in","My last answer wasn't complete . . . I thought I could ise","My last answer wasn't complete . . . I thought I could isn","My last answer wasn't complete . . . I thought I could is","My last answer wasn't complete . . . I thought I could insert line breaks with the Enter key.  I believe it is always a generator.  Based on the generator definition","My last answer wasn't complete . . . I thought I could insert line breaks with the Enter key.  I believe it is always a generator.  This is the formula shown on the genear","My last answer wasn't complete . . . I thought I could insert line breaks with the Enter key.  I believe it is always a generator.  This is the formula shown o","My last answer wasn't complete . . . I thought I could insert line breaks with the Enter key.  I believe it is always a generator.  This is the formula shown in the generato ","My last answer wasn't complete . . . I thought I could insert line breaks with the Ent er key.   I believe it is always a generator.  This is the formula shown in the generator definition, ","My last answer wasn't complete . . . I thought I could insert line breaks with the Enter key.  I believe it is always a generator.  This is the formula shown in the generator definition,","My last answer wasn't complete . . . I thought I could insert line breaks with the Enter key.  I believe it is always a generator.  This is the formula shown in the generator definition."],"rt":249631,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":1352992,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Never","response_history":["Never"],"rt":91023,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":1444019,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press \"Continue\" to continue.","rt":4247,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":1448271,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"36","response_history":["36"],"rt":3351,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":1451625,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Masters Degree","response_history":["Masters Degree"],"rt":2904,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":1454534,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Calc II Honors","response_history":["Calc II Honors"],"rt":7497,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":1462037,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":4636,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":1466676,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":3073,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":1469755,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":3453,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":1473212,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the conc epts in  this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":2437,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":1475653,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - definitely","response_history":["3 - definitely"],"rt":2672,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":1478328,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Male","response_history":["Male"],"rt":1980,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":1480313,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What i s/are yo ur native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","response_history":["English"],"rt":4221,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":1484537,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":4034,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":1488575,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I wish I could revisit some of my answers.  I think I have a better understanding now than I did about halfway through the exercise.","response_history":["I wish I ou","I wish I o","I wish I coudl ","I wish I coudl","I  wish I  coud","I wish I could revisit some of my answers.  I think I have a a","I wish I could revisit some of my answers.  I think I have a better understanding now than a","I wish I could revisit some of my answers.  I think I have a better understanding now than I did at","I wish I could revisit some of my answers.  I think I have a better understanding now than I did about halfway throgh ","I wish I could revisit some of my answers.  I think I have a better understanding now than I did about halfway throgh","I wish I could revisit some of my answers.  I think I have a better understanding now than I did about halfway throg","I wish I could revisit some of my answers.  I think I have a better understanding now than I did about halfway through the exercies","I wish I could revisit some of my answers.  I think I have a better understanding now than I did about halfway through the exercie","I wish I could revisit some of my answers.  I think I have a better understanding now than I  did abou t halfway through the exercise."],"rt":28753,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":1517332,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"}]